RG 005:038, Office of the Governor: Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. (1991-1995)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Press Files, 1991-1994; 1995-031
  - Workforce predictions, 1991 October 3 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Gov. Wicker announces grants to municipalities, 1991 October 4 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Lincoln portrait (sheet music), 1991 October 5 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Office of Policy and Management (OPM) repeal option, undated (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Reappointment Commission, 1991 October 5 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Appointments to Export Trade Panel, 1991 October 7 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Appointments to State board of Mediation and Arbitration, 1991 October 7 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Gov. Weicker makes various appointments, 1991 October 7 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Appointments to municipal training, 1991 October 8 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Appointments to Connecticut State Employees Retirement Commission, 1991 October 9 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Appointments to State Insurance Purchasing Board, 1991 October 9 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Chubb Fellow lecture, 1991 October 9 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Appointments to Department of Education Arbitration Panel, 1991 October 16 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Layoff tally report, 1991 October 17 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Moody's rates Connecticut economic recovery, 1991 October 21 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - 1991 food drive, 1991 October 22 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Advocate news clip, "Weicker resolute on personal income tax", 1991 October 24 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Gov. Wicker's convocation address at Gallaudet University, 1991 October 25 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Connecticut Poll, state politics and budget, 1991 October 27 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - National Governors" Association (NGA) report mailed to General Assembly, 1991 October 30 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Financial statement of October 31, 1991, Curry's letter to Gov. Weicker, 1991 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Forest Practices Advisory Board, 1991 November 4 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Work schedule reductions, 1991 November 6 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - California car put in neutral by Connecticut officials, 1991 November 7 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Industrial Expansion in Bozrah, 1991 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Executive summary, undated (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - State Tax Review Commission appointments, 1991 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Where does the money go?, undated (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - What is an income tax?, undated (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - A Campaign for Connecticut, major plan to reach out to business, 1991 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Gov. Weicker releases labor proposal, 1991 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Gov. Weicker attends first meeting of Greater Bridgeport Recovery Economic Development Commission, 1991 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Statement on release of the union proposal, 1991 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Tool company relocates in Bridgeport, 1991 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Dept. of Revenue Services (DRS) releases 1992 withholding tables and forms, 1991 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Gov. Weicker seeks advice on disposal facility, 1991 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Gov. Weicker reviews budget, 1991-1992, 1991 November 18 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Tax revenue shortfall 1991-1992 state budget, 1991 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Recommended fees, General Fund, undated (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Gov. Weicker announces tax revenue shortfall, 1991 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Gov. Weicker announces startup grant for innovative New London shellfish company, 1991 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - State establishes network to assist defense diversification, 1991 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Work schedule reductions, 1991 November 20 (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Update on layoffs, 1991 November 21 (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Work schedule reductions, 1991 November 26 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - $120 million in new federal income may come to Connecticut Uncompensated Care Pool, 1991 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Berlin manufacturer expands with state and town assistance, 1991 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Howmet to expand Winsted site, 1991 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - State program assists Pomfret food producer, 1991 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Lambert Day to expand in Winchester Business Park, 1991 November 29 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Tours of the Governor's Residence, 1991 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Hours extended at Governor's Residence, 1991 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Repeal at any price? by Office of Policy and Management (OPM), 1991 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - 50th anniversary of Pearl Harbor, 1991 December 6 (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Appointments to State board of Mediation and Arbitration, 1991 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Governor makes appointments, 1991 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Office of Fiscal Analysis fiscal note on S.H.B. 9010, 1991 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - Gov. Weicker remarks on alternative budget to Stanley Forum, New Britain, 1991 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Gov. Weicker comments on alternative budget, 1991 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Why an uncompensated care pool makes sense for Connecticut, 1991 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - Council on Mental Retardation, 1991 December 10 (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - Judicial nominations, 1991 December 11 (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - Emergency certified bill 9010, November Special Session, 1991 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Funding for advanced technology centers on University of Connecticut and Yale, 1991 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Layoff and furloughs suspended, 1991 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - State investment in unique diabetes treatment method, 1991 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - Appointments to the Martin Luther King, Jr. Commission, 1991 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - Appointments to Victim Services Coordinating Council, 1991 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - Cibes letter to Curry, 1991 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - State and Mashantucket Pequot tribe reach agreement, 1991 December 17 (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - Connecticut becomes first state to implement partnerships to fund long term health care, 1991 December 18 (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - Appointments to the Board of Examiners for Nursing, 1991 December 19 (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - Appointments to Connecticut Humanities Council, 1991 December 19 (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - Bill signing, 1991 December 19 (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - State tentatively approves $15 million in financing for Remington Products, 1991 December 23 (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - Connecticut receives $5.8 million from Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1991 December 24 (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - Gov. Weicker announces staff appointments, 1991 December 27 (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - Gov. Weicker unveils plan for quality integrated schools, 1992 January 6 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Appointments, 1992 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on Jim Mulvihill, 1992 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Special election, 77th General Assembly district, 1992 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Dominic Forsella to head Connecticut waste management agency, 1992 January 13 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ribicoff letter, 1992 January 13 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Decision made for Housatonic Community College site in Bridgeport, 1992 January 13 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Gov. Weicker meets with state employee volunteers, 1992 January 14 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Appointments to Workers" Compensation Commission, 1992 January 16 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Rockbestos to stay in Connecticut, 1992 January 16 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - John Blum named new Agriculture Commissioner, 1992 January 17 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mount Trashmore agreement, 1992 January 24 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Letter to Barrows and Anastasia regarding Somers, 1992 January 29 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Initiative to expand school based health centers, 1992 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Gov. Weicker makes appointments, 1992 January 31 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Southeastern Connecticut defense diversification, 1992 January 31 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Gov. Weicker's State of the State message, 1992 February 5 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Gov. Weicker's budget message, 1992 February 13 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 1991-1992 Copies of newspaper articles on Gov. Weicker on the income tax (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Gov. Weicker announces grant award for healthy planning from Johnson Foundation, 1992 February 24 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Gov Weicker's Public Safety Committee testimony, 1992 February 27 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Gov. Weicker announces state acquisition of four important open space parcels, 1992 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Nominations to Milk Board and Visitors" Panels, 1992 March 2 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bills signed, 1992 March 4 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - King Holiday Commission & other panels members named, 1992 March 5 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - New Adjutant General named at National Guard, Col. David Gay, 1992 March 11 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Executive Order #1, 1992 March 13 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Executive Order #2, 1992 March 13 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Explanatory detail for Dept. of Income Maintenance (DIM) 1992-1993 proposed budget, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Gov. Weicker's Commerce & Exploration Committee testimony, 1992 March 19 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Agreement with Gas Company on oyster beds, 1992 March 27 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Bills signed, 1992 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Gov. Weicker's speech at Kennedy School of Government, 1992 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Appointment of Robert Werner as Deputy Commissioner of Department of Children and Youth Services (DCYS), 1992 April 3 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Appointment to environmental panel and other boards, 1992 April 7 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - February budget recommended layoff, 1992 April 8 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Statement on MIAs, Vietnam, 1992 April 9 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Copy of magazine article, 'the State of the States", 1992 April 22 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Gov. Weicker announces additional hurricane aid distribution, 1992 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Bills signed, 1992 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Connecticut Alliance for Home Ownership Opportunities, press packets, 1992 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bills signed, 1992 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Phantom Casinos, Office of Policy and Management (OPM), 1992 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Executive Order #8, 1992 May (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Bills signed, 1992 May 5 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Veto H.B. 5536, 1992 May 5 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Budget bill signed, 1992 May 6 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Gov. Weicker's closing comments, 1992 legislative session, 1992 May 6 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Gov. Weicker announces approval of bonding for mayor state projects, 1992 May 8 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Gov. Weicker announces land acquisition and environmental bond authorizations, 1992 May 8 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Bills signed, 1992 May 11 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - State files motion to modify Dept. of Children and Youth Services (DCYS) consent decree, 1992 May 11 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Gov. Weicker House Budget Committee testimony, 1992 May 15 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Richard Orluk named Executive Assistant in Division of Special Revenue, 1992 May 15 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Gov. Weicker 1992 JFK Profile in Courage award winner, 1992 May 18 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Bills signed, 1992 May 19 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Bills signed at 3:30 PM, 1992 May 20 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Bills signed, 1992 May 20 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Reward letter for murder of Lawrence Biller and Brice Horowitz, 1992 May 20 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Transfer of state land to Town of Enfield for soccer field, 1992 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Waterbury company announces $10.5 million state assisted expansion, 1992 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Bills signed, 1992 May 22 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - HIV testing Bill 373 signed at Stamford, 1992 May 22 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Bills signed, 1992 May 26 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Bills signed, 1992 May 26 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - State launches marketing campaign for economic development, 1992 May 26 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Bills signed, 1992 May 27 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints sexual violence task force, 1992 May 27 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Gov. Weicker's Profile in Courage Award JFK Library speech, 1992 May 28 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Bills signed, labeling dangerous toys, 1992 May 29 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Bills signed, 1992 May 29 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Economic development legislation, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Bills signed AM, 1992 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Bills signed PM, 1992 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Copy of newspaper article on John F. Kennedy's legacy, 1992 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Bills signed AM, 1992 June 2 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Bills signed PM, 1992 June 2 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Gov. Weicker announces appointment of commission on educational excellence for Connecticut, 1992 June 2 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - New director of Emergency Management, 1992 June 2 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Bills signed, 1992 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Bills signed and bills vetoed, 1992 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Veto message on H.B. 5603, P.A. 92-175, 1992 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Veto message on S.B. 491, S.A. 92-17, 1992 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Bills signed, 1992 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Mark Waxenberg and Jeff Stewart appointments, 1992 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Veto message H.B. 5871, 1992 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Veto message on H.B. 5148, P.A. 92-163, 1992 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Robert Santy, Department of Environmental Protection (DEP) Commissioner, 1992 June 5 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Bills signed, 1992 June 8 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Bills signed, 1992 June 8 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Federal teams survey flood damage, 1992 June 8 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Bills signed, 1992 June 9 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Connecticut makes aggressive bid for 1995 Special Olympics World Games, 1992 June 10 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Bills signed, 1992 June 11 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Bills signed, 1992 June 11 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Bills signed special session, 1992 June 11 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Call of the Special Session, 1992 June 11 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Engrossed bills, 1992 June 11 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Special session agenda to include firearms legislation, 1992 June 11 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Gov. Weicker meets with Education Commissioner and Student Advisory Council on Education, 1992 June 11 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Advisory to media re Imus show, 1992 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Disaster relief request letter, 1992 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Gov. Weicker seeks federal disaster aid, damage estimates now top $10 million, 1992 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - List of bills signed and vetoed, 1992 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Special Session bills, 1992 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Veto message S.H.B. 5888, P.A. 92-258, 1992 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Veto message S.S.B. 490, P.A. 92-226, 1992 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Veto message S.H.B. 5862, P.A. 82-225, 1992 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Veto message H.B. 5846, P.A. 92-256, 1992 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Veto message S.H.B. 5269, S.A. 92-18, 1992 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Veto message, S.H. 5895, S.A. 92-26, 1992 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Gov. Weicker signs sweeping economic development legislation, 1992 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Message on S.H.B. 5858, S.A. 92-27, 1992 June 13 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Gov. Weicker's statement regarding gifts of any kind, Ethics Commission, 1992 June 15 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Gov. Weicker's response to Larson regarding Mashantucket Pequot Indian casino, 1992 June 16 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates Flemming L. Norcott, Jr. as Justice of the Connecticut Supreme Court, 1992 June 18 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Gov. Weicker's proposal to combat youth gun violence, 1992 June 18 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Bills signed PM, 1992 June 19 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Bills signed Special Session, 1992 June 19 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints 5 people to Superior Court, 1992 June 19 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Tom Benedict nominated to Dept. of Public Utility and Contol (DPUC) Authority, 1992 June 24 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Letter to Bridgeport Mayor Ganim from Bill Cibes, 1992 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Commissioner Cioffi's memo on handguns, 1992 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Bills vetoed Special Session, 1992 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Veto S.B. 2900, Special Session, 1992 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Connecticut seeks International Special Olympics, Governor to meet with site selection committee, 1992 June 26 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - E. Cortright Phillips named to Commission on Hospitals and Health Care, 1992 June 26 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Gov. Weicker announces financing for state projects, 1992 June 26 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Gov. Weicker's statement concerning abortion ruling by the U.S. Supreme Court, 1992 June 29 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Fleet National named first "Preferred lender" with $200 million to break credit crunch, 1992 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Gov. Weicker announces appointment of Greenways Committee, 1992 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Connecticut to host 1995 Special Olympics World Summer Games, 1992 July 1 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Foxwoods Casino memo of understanding, 1992 July 2 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Gov. Weicker announces U.S. small business aid available to businesses, homeowners, renters at regional centers, 1992 July 2 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Gov. Weicker manes 22 people to Birth to Three Council, 1992 July 7 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - June Special Session bills signed, 1992 July 7 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Dr. Canonetti resigns as University of Connecticut Board Chairman, 1992 July 8 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - New members appointed to CII Board and Finance Advisory Commission, 1992 July 8 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Gov. Weicker announces $1.8 million urban initiative funds are earmarked for children in ten cities, 1992 July 9 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints Lewis B. Rome as Chairman of University of Connecticut Board of Trustees, 1992 July 9 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - SBA loan application centers will remain open one additional week, 1992 July 9 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Proposals sought to develop Groton Marine Science/Tech Center, 1992 July 10 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates five people to State Library Board, 1992 July 13 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Gov. Weicker announces Bridgeport park and zoo acquisition and praises open state preservation for cities, 1992 July 14 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Letter to William Curry from Commisioner Allan Crystal, 1992 July 15 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints three people to Commission on Educational Excellence, 1992 July 15 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Gov. Weicker's letter to Mr. Clayton Gengras, Jr., Chairman, Connecticut Convention Center Authority, 1992 July 15 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Gov. Woecker nominates Edward C. Ewing to Gaming Board, 1992 July 17 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Offer of reward letter in Connection with the murder of Arthur Newkirk, 1992 July 21 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - David Hayes honor, 1992 July 22 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - A comparison: The fiscal year 1881-1992 v. Coalition III, 1992 July 23 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Bills signed, June 1992 Special Session, 1992 July 23 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Frankl, Chairman of Workers" Compensation Commission, 1992 July 23 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Bond Commission approves down payment assistance, housing initiatives, 1992 July 24 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Financing for state project, defense diversification and high tech, 1992 July 24 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - State purchases development rights to Lebanon farm, 1992 July 24 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Gov. Weicker, A Connecticut Party convention speech, 1992 July 25 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates two to Gambling Task Force, 1992 July 27 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Mary Collier named to interagency post, 1992 July 28 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Appointments to Chiropractic Board and Committee on Physical Fitness, 1992 July 30 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Gov. Weicker makes appointment to Hospital Commission, Board of Governors for Higher Education, 1992 July 30 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Southbury Training School Board members, 1992 July 30 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Gov. Weicker seeks support of long-term care policy, plans to address issue at summer NGA meeting in Princeton, NJ, 1992 July 31 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints Task Force on Justice for Abused Children, 1992 August 5 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Lt. Gov. Groark receives food baskets from Commissioner Blum, 1992 August 11 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Gov. Weicker's appointment of Commissioner Prague to Physician Advisory Committee, 1992 August 14 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Reward letter for murder of John Tadduni, 1992 August 17 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Strong consumer interest in new long-term care insurance policies, 1992 August 17 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Kerite Division to stay, build new facility in Seymour, 1992 August 20 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Gov. Weicker, O-Z Gedney, 1992 August 25 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Gov. Weicker, O-Z Gedney, $6 million package, 350 jobs retained, 1992 August 25 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Connecticut Wine Trail dedication of Haight Vineyard in Litchfield, 1992 August 26 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints five to Film Commission, 1992 August 26 (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Gwen Weltman appointment to Hospital Commission, 1992 August 27 (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Tentative agreement between Oak Hill Board and members of District 1199, 1992 August 27 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Gov. Weicker comments on G.M. plans to sell Delco chassis, 1992 August 28 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Gov. Weicker suggests Hurricane Andrew aid be sent through Red Cross and Salvation Army, 1992 August 28 (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - Gov. Weicker announces financing for businesses and human services, 1992 August 28 (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - State purchases development rights to Washington farm, 1992 August 28 (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints Louziotis and Werner to new positions within the administration, 1992 September 1 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - Office of Policy and Management (OPM) fact sheet on 1991-1992 budget, 1992 September 1 (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - Reward letter on four arson fires in the City of New Britain, 1992 September 1 (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - Watertown chosen by Torrington company for new manufacturing plant, 1992 September 3 (Box 2, Folder 183)
  - Werner names new deputy executive director, 1992 September 9 (Box 2, Folder 184)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on G. Fox, 1992 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 185)
  - Canberra Industries to relocate to Meriden, 400 jobs retained, 1992 September 16 (Box 2, Folder 186)
  - State - People's Bank $15 million loan retains Remington Products in Bridgeport, 1992 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 187)
  - Milford Rivet and Machine Co. to remain in Connecticut, 1992 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 188)
  - Miles Research Center dedication, 1992 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 189)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates Joette Katz as Justice to Connecticut Supreme Court, 1992 September 18 (Box 2, Folder 190)
  - Draft of Taborsak acceptance speech at A Connecticut Party convention, 1992 September 20 (Box 2, Folder 191)
  - Kids are winners in new school readiness program, 1992 September 21 (Box 2, Folder 192)
  - State to invest $3 million to diversify Kaman Aerospace, 1992 September 21 (Box 2, Folder 193)
  - Gov. Weicker remarks at Connecticut Association of Realtors, 1992 September 22 (Box 2, Folder 194)
  - Gov. Weicker announces Bond Commission financing of new State Police headquarters, housing, and jobs, 1992 September 25 (Box 2, Folder 195)
  - State purchases development rights to two eastern Connecticut farms, 1992 September 25 (Box 2, Folder 196)